All right. So, we have our mini batches of data and now it's time to define our model.
好的创建迷你批次数据后 现在该定义模型了
This is a little diagram of what the model will look like.
此图表显示了模型的结构
We'll have our character's put into our input layer and then a stack of LSTM cells.
将这些字符传入输入层 然后堆叠 LSTM 单元
These LSTM cells make up our hidden recurrent layer and when they look at a mini batch of
这些 LSTM 单元构成了隐藏递归层 将迷你批次的数据传入这些递归层时
data as input they'll look at one character at
它们将一次查看一个字符
a time and produce an output and a hidden state.
并生成输出和隐藏状态
So, we will pass an input character into
我们将输入字符传入第一个 LSTM 单元
our first LSTM cell which produces a hidden state.
该单元生成一个隐藏状态
Then at the next time step,
在下个时间步
we'll look at the next character in our sequence and pass that into
查看序列中的下个字符并将该字符传入此 LSTM 单元中
this LSTM cell which will see the previous hidden state as input.
同时将上个隐藏状态当做输入
You have so far seen this behavior in a one layer RNN but in this case we
你已经在单层 RNN 中见过此行为
plan on using a two-layer model that has stacked LSTM layers and
但是在此例中 我们打算使用双层模型 将 LSTM 层级堆叠起来
that means that the output of this LSTM layer is going to go to the next one as
所以此 LSTM 层的输出将作为输入进入下个层级
input and each of these cells is sharing
每个单元都会
its hidden state with the next cell in the unrolled series.
与展开层级中的下个单元分享隐藏状态
Finally, the output of the last LSTM layer will include
最后一个 LSTM 层级的输出
some character class scores that will be the length of our vocabulary.
将包含一些字符类别分数 长度等于词汇表的长度
We'll put this through a Softmax activation function which we'll use to get
对此输出应用 Softmax 激活函数
the probability distribution for predicting the most likely next character.
并获得概率分布以预测下个最有可能的字符
So, to start you off on this task,
为了帮助你开始此任务
you've been given some skeleton code for creating a model.
我们提供了创建模型的框架代码
First, we're going to check to see if a GPU is
首先 我们将检查是否有 GPU 可用于训练
available for training then you'll see this class character RNN.
然后是这个 CharRNN 类
You can see that this character RNN class has
这个类包含
our usual init and forward functions and later
常见的 init 和 forward 函数
you've been given some code to initialize the hidden state of
我们提供了初始化 LSTM 层级隐藏状态的代码
an LSTM layer and I'll go over this in a moment.
稍后我会讲解这些代码的
You can definitely take a look at this given code and how we're
你可以自己查看下这些代码
creating our initial character dictionaries but you won't need to change it.
看看我们是如何创建初始字符字典的 但是不需要更改代码
We also have several parameters that are going to be passed in when a character
在实例化 CharRNN 时我们会传入几个参数
RNN is instantiated and I've saved some of these as class variables.
我将其中几个参数的值保存为类变量
So, using these input parameters and variables,
你需要使用这些输入参数和变量
it will be up to you to create our model layers and complete the forward function.
创建模型层级并完成 forward 函数
You'll first create an LSTM layer which you can read about in the documentation here.
首先需要创建一个 LSTM 层级 你可以点击此链接并阅读 LSTM 文档
We can see that an LSTM layer is created using our usual parameters;
我们可以使用常见的参数创建 LSTM 层级
an input size, hidden size,
这些参数包括 input_size、hidden_size
number of layers, and a batch first parameter.
num_layers 和 batch_first
We'll also add a dropout value.
还需要添加 dropout 值
This introduces a dropout layer in between the outputs
如果你决定堆叠多个层级
of LSTM layers if you've decided to stack multiple layers.
此值将在 LSTM 层级的输出之间引入丢弃层
So, after you define an LSTM layer,
定义 LSTM 层级之后
I'll ask you to define two more layers;
还需要定义两个层级
one dropout layer and a final fully-connected layer for getting our desired output size.
一个是丢弃层 一个是最终全连接层 后者用于获取期望的输出大小
Once you've defined these layers,
定义好这些层级之后
you'll move on to define the forward function.
需要定义 forward 函数
This takes in an input x and hidden state.
参数包括输入 x 和隐藏状态
You'll pass this input through the layers of
你需要使此输入经过模型层级
the model and return a final output and hidden state.
并返回最终输出和隐藏状态
You'll have to make sure to shape the LSTM output
确保改变 LSTM 输出的形状
so that it can be fed into the last fully connected layer.
使其能够传入最终全连接层
Okay. Then at the bottom here,
Ok在底部
you'll see this function for initializing the hidden state of an LSTM.
是一个初始化 LSTM 隐藏状态的函数
An LSTM has a hidden and a cell state that are saved as a tuple hidden.
LSTM 有一个隐藏状态和单元状态 它们存储为元组 hidden
The shape of the hidden and cell state is
隐藏状态和单元状态的形状由以下参数决定：
defined first by the number of layers in our model,
模型的层级数量
the batch size of our input,
输入的批次大小
and then the hidden dimension that we specified in model creation.
以及在创建模型时指定的隐藏维度
In this function, we're initializing the hidden weights all to
在此函数中 我们将隐藏状态全初始化为 0
zero and moving them to GPU if it's available.
如果有 GPU 则移到 GPU 上
Okay, so all the code that you see you don't need to change,
你不需要更改看到的所有这些代码
you just need to define the model layers and feedforward behavior.
只需定义模型层级和前馈行为
If you've implemented this correctly,
如果代码实现正确
you should be able to set your model hyperparameters
你应该能够设置模型超参数
and proceed with training and generating some sample text.
继续训练模型并生成一些示例文本
Try this out on your own then next,
自己尝试一下
check out my solution.
然后看看我的答案